HUY DO

RUBY ON RAILS - WEB DEVLOPER

I really love being a web developer.

Currently, I'm working with Rails but still open to any position related to web development.

PERSONALITY HIGHLIGHTS

- Motivated by problem solving
- Independent worker
- Works well with deadlines
- Collaborative and efficient
- Love sharing knowledge

CONTACT DETAILS

Address:

E Home S Department, District 9, Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam.

Email:

huydo91@outlook.com

Phone:

+84869112601

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/huy-do-772b32143

Projects:

https://jackiedo91.github.io/jackie_do_blog/projects/

BASIC INFORMATION

Just a guy has a little passion to build wonderful websites, delivery the best quality to customers.

I'm a Ruby on Rails web developer with almost 2 years of experience in various fields of web development: Frontend, Back-end and Server Administration.

Like challenging myself, dare to take responsibilities, enjoy coding and learning new things everyday.

"Keep doing it while your eyes and hands can handle. Sooner or later one of the two will fail you and that work will be a great reminder of just how much talent you gave the world."

EDUCATION

University of Science — Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam (2010 - 2014) Bachelor Degree in Software Development

Still want to learn as many as possible..

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Web Developerr, NUS Technology, Viet Nam (Sep 2016 - Present)

I'm taking responsibilities for developing and maintaining a service website of Box at Work Germany startup that received Series A funding of € 5,5 million, Box at Work, Europe's leading on-demand Self Storage platform. Currently operating in 16 cities in Germany, France, Netherlands and United States.

Professional Analyst Programmer, CSC, Viet Nam (Jan 2015 - Aug 2016).

Analyzing business requirements from Singapore clients and transform to technical specifications
Working alongside other developers to maintain and implement a huge system in various fields of Insurance industry.

Have worked onsite in Singapore to go live the product of Tokio Marine Singapore.